

Camille Buan

Electronic Data Interchange Coordinator/Accounting Professional

+63 975 059 0192 📞

buancamillee@gmail.com 🔀

https://www.linkedin.com/in/camillebuan/ in



https://github.com/csbuan

About Me

Highly motivated and analytical professional with more than two years of working experience in the field of Accounting and Finance looking for a challenging role that requires constant learning and development. Her interests include programming, problem-solving, analyzing complex data, strategic planning, project management, anything and that requires analytical/critical thinking.

Technical Skills

HTML JavaScript Python Computer Science Figma

Soft Skills

Public speaking

Attention to detail

Time management

Project Management

Communication Skills

Work Experience

Feb 2022 -Present New York, United States

Electronic Data Interchange Coordinator/Accounting Clerk **Diversified Global Solutions**

Supervising inventories and ensuring that all reports and data entries are accurate in the system. In charge of processing the orders in compliance with the clients' guidelines. Responsible for manual invoicing of sales orders and managing all open orders. Addressing questions about shipments and deliveries. Checking of invoice request's details accuracy in the records.

2019-2021 Alabang, Philippines

Accounting Assistant | Fast Services Corporation

Prepared reports and presented results to the CEO. Weekly reporter of the movement of overall Cash Advances to the CEO and Site managers. Prepared and monitored financial data in the database (SAP). Reduced the major and minor Audit Findings during the 2021 Audit in Accounting. Awarded as Best Presenter, represented the General Accounting Department. Spearheaded the team for a whole quarter as a team leader.

2018-2018 Makati Philippines

Accounting Intern | Golden Arches Development Corporation

Prepared the company's Disbursement Funding Forecast. In charge of preparing vouchers, receipts, checks, and journal entries. Made manual checks, printouts, and processed checks. Also helped with the Treasury Department from time to time.

Courses & Trainings

The Web Developer Bootcamp 2022

Udemy

Intermediate HTML and CSS

The Odin Project

CS50's Introduction to Computer Science

Harvard University

Responsive Web Design

Free Code Camp

Data Analysis with Python

Coursera

Accounting Fundamentals

Corporate Finance Institute (CFI)

Excel Crash Course Spreadsheet Formulas for Finance

Corporate Finance Institute (CFI)

Education

Bachelor of Science in Business Management major in Financial **Management** (2015 - 2019) GPA: 1.36

- Graduated Magna Cum Laude
- Student leader for two academic years, 2017-2019
- 2nd Round Qualifier in JCFAP's Top Ten Outstanding Finance Students 2018
- Consistent University Full Scholar and Provincial Scholar
- Acquired the highest GPA in the College of Economics, Management, and Development Studies during the 1st Semester of S.Y. 2017-2018. (with a GPA of 1.11)